strongmenstayyoung.com 2019-06-24

# Our Privacy Policy at Strong Men Stay Young

Here at **Strong Men Stay Young** we do our best to respect your privacy. We know that your privacy is important to you, so it is important to us. 

**Private Information**   
As regards any purchase you may make of products offered on this site, for your safety and protection your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, (ClickBank), keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf. Visit this [ClickBank Customer Privacy](http://www.clickbank.com/customer_privacy.html) page to learn more about their privacy policy. 

**Email**   
We store no personal information about you, other than your email address, if you should offer it to us. You might do this in order to receive a download link. For example, if you were to purchase the ebook on this site, your download link will be mailed to you. You might also supply your email address to receive ongoing information about how to improve your health through the practices outlined in detail in our product. 

Specifically, Strong Men Stay Young may generate e-mail for the following types of communication: 

1\. Notification e-mail to which the individual may subscribe and unsubscribe. 

2\. Transactional e-mail, which is the result of a business transaction initiated with Strong Men Stay Young. 

3\. Relationship e-mail, which is sent as an informational service because of a relationship with Strong Men Stay Young. 

4\. Correspondence from Strong Men Stay Young as a result of a communication initiated by a member or customer. 

E-mail that has a provision for opt-out (which is any newsletter to which you might have subscribed to on this site) will include instructions on how to do so. Specifically, you will find an unsubscribe link at the bottom of all non-personal subscription-based emails. 

Strong Men Stay Young may occasionally send informational or promotional materials to members and customers. You may choose to exclude yourself from these mailings by unsubscribing at any time. 

Note: Your email address is never made available to any third party, so you need not worry about accruing extra spam in your in-box simply because you offer us your email address. 

**HTTP Cookies**   
A HTTP Cookie is a piece of data that is stored by your browser in either your computer's memory or on your computer's hard drive. Strong Men Stay Young uses cookies to keep track of user session identity on the website, such as tracking items in a shopping cart. Cookies may also be used to track the effectiveness of various services provided on Strong Men Stay Young website. 

We may also use cookies to track affiliate referrals, and to determine whether or not we might have already presented a particular piece of information to you. Cookies therefore add a measure of convenience when surfing this site. 

**Other Sites**   
This Privacy Statement only addresses Strong Men Stay Young use and disclosure of the information we collect from you. The Strong Men Stay Young website may contain links to other websites. Strong Men Stay Young is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other websites. To the extent that you visit or disclose personal information to other websites, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of these other websites. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose any personal information. 

**Transmission Errors or Unauthorized Acts**   
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Strong Men Stay Young cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Strong Men Stay Young will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. However, once we receive your transmission, we do our best to ensure its security on our systems by making reasonable efforts to protect the information. 

**Security**   
Any information provided to Strong Men Stay Young is treated with care and discretion. Strong Men Stay Young will take a proactive approach to ensure the information is kept private and not misused. 

**Policy Changes**   
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change onward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check the current page on our web site periodically. 

Any aggregate visitor information we collect is used for internal review only and is then discarded. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us to request more information. 

**Contact Information**   
You can find an email form to contact us online, and our address on our [Contact Us Page](https://strongmenstayyoung.com/strongmen/contact/).
